剧情回顾...
我见到了我的亲生父亲
I met my real father.
好消息  不是么?
Great news, right?
他假装很爱我
He pretended to love me
为的就是要偷走我的肾
just long enough to steal my kidney.
我昨晚一直跟着你
I followed you last night.
那是你父亲的房子吗?
Is it your father's house?
你以后不会再去那个地方了
you're not gonna go to that place anymore.
好的
All right.
你认为
You think
你是第一个被骗的人么?
you're the first person that ever got conned?
你需要一个父亲 而我需要一个肾
You needed a father figureand I needed a kidney.
-嘿  Helen...  -你得做出选择
-Hey, Helen...  -You're gonna have to choose.
他还是我
Him or me.
我叫Henry Gale   我从明尼苏达来
My name is Henry Gale. I'm from Minnesota.
你画一张去你热气球那儿的地图
You draw up a map to your balloon.
我们就会去那儿找到它的
We go out there, we find it.
如果我画错了  他们会杀了我
And if I mess up, they'll crucify me.
你到底知不知道它在哪儿?
Do you or do you not know where it is?
我在那儿葬了我的妻子
I went back there to bury my wife.
是去他热气球那儿的
It's to his balloon.
这至少要走一天
This is at least a day's walk.
那我们现在就动身
Then we should get going.
他说过热气球就在这儿
This is where he said it would be.
-我们得确定一下  -如果我是他们中的一个
-We need to be sure.  -If I was one of them,
那些你们认为是敌人的人
these people that you seem to think are your enemies,
那儿就不会有什么热气球了
there'd be no balloon.
我会画一张去一个隐秘的地方的地图
So I'd draw a map to a real secluded place.
当你们的朋友到那儿时
And when your friends got there,
一群我的人就会在那儿等他们了
a bunch of my people'd be waiting for them.
还好我不是他们的一员  不是么?
I guess it's a good thing I'm not one of them, huh?
-我做了什么你要带我去郊游?  -什么?
-So, what did I do to deserve this?  -What?
一个小伙子就不能带他的女朋友
Can't a fella take his girl
出去野餐吗?还得要原因?
out for a picnic lunch just 'cause?
"小伙子"?
"Fella"?
是的  小伙子
That's right. Fella.
那么  你准备带我去哪?
So, where you taking me?
我不会说的  你别问了
I'm not telling, so just quit asking.
没有我能帮上忙的吗?
Can I be of any help?
你就看讣告  喝咖啡就行了
You just read your obituaries and drink your coffee
所有的事情我来处理
and I'll take care of the everything.
别看不起讣告
Don't knock the obits;
这是报纸最有意思的部分
it's the nicest part of the paper.
人一旦死了就不会有人再对他说三道四
No one ever says anything mean about people once they're dead.
恩  在我看来
Mm. And here I am thinking
连环画才是报纸上最有意思的部分
the funnies are the nicest part of the paper.
John?
John  你父亲叫什么?
John, what's your father's name?
怎么了?
Why?
是叫Anthony么?
Is it Anthony?
Anthony Cooper
是的  是叫这个名字
Yes. That's right.
他死了
He's dead.
再画一遍
Draw it again,
去你热气球那儿的地图
the map to your balloon.
我在开玩笑  一个玩笑罢了
I was joking. I was making a joke.
那儿除了我的热气球就没别的了
There's nothing out there besides my balloon.
我只是太沮丧了
I was just frustrated.
这么说太愚蠢了
It was a stupid thing to say.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
无论如何  现在太晚了
It's too late anyway.
她已经走出很远了  Jack
She's already long gone, Jack.
那么  该做的都做了
So, what's done is done?
是的
That's right.
把他带回武器库去
Put him back in the armory.
为什么让他对你这么说话?
Why do you let him talk to you like that?
等等  我...
Hey, wait, I...
闭嘴
Shut up.
John  我很抱歉
John, I'm sorry.
John
也许他画错了
Maybe he's wrong.
我们应该找找悬崖另一边
We should search the other side of the cliff.
我们已经找了三小时了
We've been searching for three hours.
热气球根本不存在  Charlie
This balloon does not exist.Charlie!
那么他为什么画这张地图?
Then why'd he draw the map?
你告诉他你会保护他的
You told him you'd protect him
不管找不找得到热气球
whether we found the balloon or not.
你又多给了他两天来拖延时间
You've given him two more days to stall,
去想怎么逃跑
to figure out how to escape.
我们到此为止了
We're done.
Charlie
在这  往这边
Over here! This way!
Sayid
他说过他埋了她  是么?
He said he buried her, right?
他的妻子?
His wife?
为什么这里没有雨?
Why isn't it raining here?
迷 失 第二季 第十七集
声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Singa校对： BillSky
后期：xyz 双语制作：DrunkBat
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
Hurley
你有看到Ana Lucia么?
have you seen Ana Lucia?
她去丛林了
She took off into the jungle
和Charlie  Sayid一起  昨天走的
with Charlie and Sayid yesterday.
昨天
Yesterday.
他们有说要去哪么?
She say anything about where they were going?
那要靠猜了
Well, that would,
每次有人告诉我什么 我都要猜他到底是什么意思
like, assume anybody actually tells me anything.
也许如果我在你们圈子里
Maybe if I were in the loop,
就能帮上点什么忙了
I could be more helpful.
根本没什么圈子  Hurley
There is no loop, Hurley.
打扰一下  Jack
Excuse me, Jack.
他全身火热还有点焦躁不安
He's been really hot and fussy.
你能看一下么?
Do you mind having a look?
-恩  好的好的  -谢谢
-Yeah. Sure, sure.  -Thanks.
圈子  伙计  圈子
Loop, dude. Loop.
那个  发烧是不是全好了?
So, the fever's completely gone?
全好了
Completely.
你不是随便说说的吧?
You're not just saying that, right?
你看起来有点心烦意乱
You seem a bit distracted.
不  我很好  Aaron也一样
I'm fine. And so is Aaron.
谢谢
Thanks.
还看诊吗?
Doctor still in?
我在涨潮抓贝类的时候
I was grabbing for mussels in the tide pool,
被海胆扎了
pissed off a sea urchin.
看起来没感染
Well, doesn't look infected.
擦点尼奥普林就没事了
A little Neosporin wouldn't hurt.
哦  好的  尼奥普林
Yeah. Right. Neosporin.
我想现在的汇率
I think the current rate of exchange is
十件衣服才换一管药膏
ten loads of laundry for a tube.
是的
Right.
怎么回事?
What was that?
John?
发生什么事了?
What's the matter?
你确定你要这么做?
You sure you want to do this?
你知道  我们可以直接去野餐的
We could just go on that picnic,you know.
很快  我保证
Soon, I promise.
也许他把他的肾留给你了
Maybe he left you his kidney.
我们活着的人
"For we who are alive, who are left
会与他们在云端重逢
will be caught up together with them in the clouds
在空中共同会见我们的主
to meet the Lord in the air,
之后就会与主同在
and so we will live with the Lord forever. "
我们把Anthony Cooper的灵魂托付给你
We commit the soul of Anthony Cooper to you,
但是我们永远不会分开
that we shall never be separated.
现在
And now
我们一起向耶稣祈祷  阿门
we are united with Christ as we go toward him. Amen.
你想说点什么么  John?
Do you wish to say anything, John?
我原谅你了
I forgive you.
John?
嘿  你在么?
Hey, you out there?
是什么声音?
What's that noise?
John?  怎么了? 说话啊
John? What's going on? Talk to me.
安静点好么?
Will you be quiet?
告诉我怎么了  到底...
Tell me what's happening. What the hell is...
你给我闭嘴
Will you shut up?
10... 9... 8...
Ten, nine, eight,
7...
seven,
6... 5... 4...
six, five, four,
也许你得叫Jack来
-Maybe you should get Jack!
3...
three,
我说了闭嘴
I said, shut up!
怎么了?
What happened?
我压四个番木瓜
I bet four papayas.
你不能压  我刚压了
You can't bet. I just bet.
你可以叫牌也可以加注
You can either call, or raise,
要么放弃
or lay 'em down, muttonchops.
别看我
Don't look at me.
放弃吧  Hurley 他牌比你大
Lay them down, Hurley. he's got you beat.
伙计  我还有杀手锏
Dude. I've got a killer hand.
不  你没有
No, you don't.
你是五张顺子
You got a baby straight.
他有同花
He's got the flush.
我呢?  我有什么?
What about me? What do I got?
很难说
Hard to say,
但你就是为了好玩
but you're just playing for the fun of it.
恩  好玩也没什么不好
Well, fun's not bad.
你偶尔也应该玩玩
You should try it sometime.
不要加注了  Hurley
Don't call him, Hurley.
嘿  职业牌手
Hey, Amarillo Slim!
你在电视上看了点扑克牌玩法
You think because you watch poker on TV
就想同高手过招?
you can tussle with the big boys?
我得回舱子里了
-I've gotta head back to the hatch.
舱子又不会自己走掉  医生
Hatch ain't going nowhere, Doc.
赢几个芒果吃怎么样?
How about you put your mangoes where your mouth is?
我想我可以玩一两把
I guess I could play a hand or two.
发生什么事了?
Hey! What's going on?
你还在吗?
Are you still out there?
John  John
我在
I'm here.
是什么声音?  怎么回事?
What were those noises? What's wrong?
没什么事
Nothing is wrong.
那么结论如何  Locke先生?
So what's the verdict, Mr. Locke?
抗震螺钉都是一等的
The seismic bolting is all first-rate,
没有长霉  没有生锈
there's no visible mold, no dry rot.
我都会写进报告里的  但是我想
It'll all be in my report,but I think
你和你丈夫是找对房子了
you and your husband got a pretty nice house here.
如果我有丈夫的话
If I had a husband,
我肯定他听到会很高兴的
I'm sure he would be happy to hear that.
你在这张发票上签个名...
If you'll just sign this invoice.
你好  儿子
Hello, Son.
你想要什么?
What do you want?
听着  John
Look, John...
我知道我这么对你是不对的
I know what I did to you was wrong.
你偷了我的肾
You stole my kidney.
我当时快要死了
I was dying.
你应该先问问我的
You could have asked me.
你想从我这里得到什么?
What do you want from me?
我假装死了是因为
I killed myself off because
外面有两个人想要我的命
there are two men who were going to beat me to it.
你做了什么  偷了他们的肝?
What did you do, steal their livers?
没有  我拿了他们七十万美元
No. I took them for 700,000 dollars.
退休前捞一笔
Retirement con.
我把钱放在一个保险箱里
I put the money in a safe deposit box,
但是那两个人很可能等在银行里
but these two guys might be sitting on the bank
看我是否会出现
to see if I show my face,
所以我才要你
which is why I need you to go in there
去那儿帮我把钱拿来
and get it for me.
你认为我是傻子?
Do you think I'm stupid?
我给你二十万
I want you to take 200 grand of it.
这弥补不了我对你的所作所为
It won't make up for what I did to you,
但我只能做这些了
but it's the best I can do.
我会在飞机场边上的旅馆
I'll be at the Flightline Motel,
一直等到明天下午
near the airport, until tomorrow afternoon.
之后不管拿不拿的到钱 我都立马走人
And then I'm gone, money or no money.
还有  John 如果到那时你还没来...
And, John, if I don't see you again...
我会理解的
I'll understand.
我们被困住了
We're locked in.
什么?
What?
这些玻璃门降下来了
These blast doors came down.
房间被封锁了
The whole living area is sealed off.
我出不去了
I can't get out.
你试着拉过...
Did you try to pry...
是的  但我不能...
Yeah, but I couldn't...
也许...
Maybe...
也许如果我们两人...
Maybe if the two of us...
你要我帮你么?
You want me to help you?
是的
Yeah.
如果我真的帮你把这些门打开了
And if I do help you get these doors up...
你又会把我关回这里  是么?
then you're gonna lock me back in here, aren't you?
是的
That's right.
那么我要你保证  John
Then I'm going to need your word, John.
我要你保证你不会让你们的人
I'm gonna need your word that you won't let your people
伤害我
do anything to me.
如果你说的是实话
Well, if you're who you say you are,
你还有什么好担心的呢?
what are you worried about?
他们出事了
Things have happened to them,
根本不关我的事
things that I had nothing to do with.
但是除了我他们找不到人来出气
But they've got no one to blame,except for me.
气都撒到我头上了
So, I'm gonna need your word...
所以我要你保证你会保护我
that you'll protect me.
无论发生什么事
No matter what.
你是谁?
Who are you?
我叫Henry Gale 我来自明尼苏达...
My name is Henry Gale. I'm from Minnesota...
我和你一样坠落在这个岛上
And I crashed on this island just like you.
好吧  我保证
All right. You have my word.
伙计  你赢了
Dude, you got me.
我不玩了
I'm out.
你知道我的牌么  医生?
Think you're in my head, Doc?
还有三个木瓜  叫牌还是认输
You've still got three papayas. Call or fold.
看来你有麻烦了  高手
Well, you're in trouble now, Cool Hand.
一对Q  这样就有三个了
Pocket Queens makes me a set.
-三个K  -喔  伙计
-Kings wired.  -Oh dube.
但至少我不知道你的牌
But at least I'm not in your head.
那么  就这样吧
Well, I guess that's it.
什么意思  就这样?
What do you mean, "it"?
Sawyer  你输光了
Sawyer, you're busted.
我全赢了  再让你去摘芒果
I got it all. Wouldn't be fair for you
我都有些过意不去了
to go and pick more mangoes.
我有更多的芒果
Well, I got a hell of a lot more than mangoes.
你还想要什么下注?  随便说
You wanna play real stakes? Name 'em.
这里已经有一堆了  伙计
It's a pile of fruit, man.
我要把它们赢回来
And I want it back.
要不要我去找个裁判来?
Should I go and get a ruler?
就到这里吧  胖子 干吗不去弄点吃的?
Fun time's over, Mongo. Why not hit the buffet?
-可我还想...  -好了  Hurley
-But, I wanna...  -Come on. Hurley.
我们走  让这些孩子自己玩吧
Let's go. Leave these boys to their sandbox.
再来一把  医生
One more hand, Doc.
赌什么?
What's it gonna take?
你从武器库偷的药品
The medicine you stole from the armory.
所有的
All of it.
准备好了吗? 1 2 3
Ready? One, two, three.
加油
Let's go.
用力些
Harder!
工具箱  把工具箱拿来  我撑着
The tool box! Get the tool box. I'll hold it.
你可以吗?
You sure?
快去
Get it!
快  快点  放到下面去
Come on! Come on! Put it under!
John  等等  你不觉得...
John, wait. Don't you think...
让门停下来
You have to stop the door.
找点其它的东西垫在下面
Put something else under the door!
快
Come on, come on!
堆起来  堆起来
Stack 'em, stack 'em.
我被压得不行了
You have to stop the pressure.
天那  快  快
Come on, come on, come on!
好了  好了  我把你弄出来
All right, all right. Let's get you out.
我拉你出来  来吧
Let's get you out, come on.
不不不  停下
No! No! Stop!
停下  停下  停下
Stop! Stop! Stop!
好吧  我们等人来  好么?
All right, we'll wait until somebody comes down. All right?
只是时间问题
It's only a matter of time.
是么?
Yeah?
不  我们没时间了
No, we don't have time.
亲爱的...
Honey.
穿上你最好的衣服
Put on your Sunday best.
我带你去野餐...
I'm taking you out to paint...
John  我们有客人
John... We have visitors.
呃  这些人说他们认识你的父亲
Um... These men say they knew your father.
John  我是Jimmy Bane
Hi, John, I'm Jimmy Bane.
我想Helen告诉过你我...
-我和他不是很熟  -她是这么说的
-I didn't really know him.  -She told me.
但我还是想问你几个问题
But I'd like to ask you a couple questions,
如果你不介意的话
if that's OK?
好  当然
Sure. Of course.
在你父亲死后你有见到过他么
Have you seen your father since he died,
Locke先生?
Mr. Locke?
我怎么可能...
How... Have I?
呃  我们在想他可能没有死
Well, we were thinking possibly he's not dead.
你也许也知道
And maybe you know that.
我是说  作为儿子
I mean, for his son,
你在他的葬礼上并没有太痛苦
you didn't look too shook up at his funeral.
你怎么敢这么说?
How dare you?
如果你知道那个男人是怎么对他的
If you had any idea what that man did to him,
那个狗娘养的... ...
what that son of a bitch...
嘿  Helen
Hey, Helen.
我们是去送他的
We were there to get past him,
让他走  我们好开始自己的生活
to get on with our lives, to let him go.
好的  好的
OK, OK.
我们走前再问一件事
Just one thing before we go.
你的包里是什么  John?
What's in the bag, John?
工作文件之类的  我是个房屋勘探员
Work papers and stuff, I'm a home inspector.
介意我看一下么?
You mind if we take a look?
恩...
Well...
就这样吧
There you go.
谢谢你的咖啡  小姐
Thanks for the coffee, miss.
Helen  我很抱歉  你没事吧?
Helen, I'm sorry. Are you OK?
你是在骗他们么  John?
Were you lying to those men, John?
没有  我当时很害怕
No, I was scared.
我只是...
I was...
我只是很害怕
I was scared.
那么  你是在哪儿学的牌  医生?
So, where'd you learn to play cards, Doc?
埔开
Phuket.
你去泰国干吗?
What the hell were you doing in Thailand?
怎么  你以为我不知道埔开在哪儿么?
What, you don't think I know where Phuket is?
我是初中没有毕业
Just 'cause I dropped out of ninth grade
可我不是傻子
don't make me an idiot.
在远东吧  是么?
Far East, huh?
看不出来你是出过远门的人
I wouldn't have taken you for a world traveler.
你在那儿刺的文身吗?
That where you got the art on your shoulder?
你再发一次牌吧?
How about you deal again?
什么?
What?
这次在桌面上发
This time from the top of the deck.
哦  我只是想试一下
Well, I had to try.
那个是用来干嘛的?
What does it do?
我们还不清楚
We're not exactly sure.
你们每隔...
And you push it...
108分钟就按一次按钮  是的
Every 108 minutes, yeah.
警报还有多久开始响?
How soon does this alarm go off?
很快  所以我要你
Very... Which is why I need you to go up
从格栅爬进通风口
through the grate and into the vents.
格栅上锁了  我试过的
Grate's bolted shut. I tried.
是的  食品室还有一个格栅
Yeah. There's another grate in the pantry.
你可以从那里出去
Get through there.
从通风口爬去屋顶
Take the vent into the dome.
也许我们可以等...
Maybe we should wait for...
我们不能等了  警报随时会响
We can't. It'll go off any minutes.
我相信你了  Henry  现在你得相信我
I trusted you, Henry. Now you gotta trust me.
按键一定要按
That button has to be pushed.
好的  我该怎么做?
OK. What do I do?
一旦你到那儿
Once you're inside,
会听到警报声
you'll hear the alarm beeping.
然后你就得输入密码
And you just have to enter the numbers:
4  8...
15  16  23  42
然后按执行键
And then you press "execute. "
密码一定要按顺序输  不能错
Exactly those numbers in exactly that order.
4  8  15  16  23  42
我记住了
I got it.
快去
Go.
你能够到么?
Can you reach it?
可以吧
I think so.
当心
Be careful.
Henry
怎么了?
What's going on?
Jack和Sawyer终于要开始一决胜负了
Jack and Sawyer are finally gonna beat each other up.
十个芒果
Ten mangoes.
好吧  我用阿司匹林跟你的牌
OK. I'll call you with the aspirin,
再加一瓶羟氨苄青霉素
and raise you a bottle of Amoxicillin.
你知道羟氨苄青霉素是什么吗?
Do you even know what Amoxicillin is?
你可能去过埔开  医生
You may have been to Phuket, Doc,
但我去过塔拉哈西
but I been to Tallahassee.
看来什么东西热起来了
Let's just say something was burning
这可不是因为阳光的原因
and it wasn't from the sunshine.
我全压了
I'm all in.
看来你是想让我放弃
Well, that's the move of a man who wants me to lay it down.
你是不会放弃的
You're not gonna lay it down.
我不会?  为什么不会?
I'm not, huh?  Why's that?
因为现在有一帮人在看我们
Because there's a bunch of people watching us right now.
你不想让他们看到你再输
and you don't want them to see you lose.
恩  好的  我跟了
Well, all right. I call.
你有什么?
What you got?
对九?
A pair of nines?
一对九你就全压了?
You pushed in with a pair of nines?
好了  看看你的吧
You caught me. Let's see 'em.
正好压住你  不是么?
Guess it was enough, huh?
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
我过会儿去拿药
I'll come get the meds later.
当我问你你要赌什么时
When I asked you what you wanted for stakes,
你为什么不说要赌枪?
why didn't you ask for the guns?
当我要枪的时候...
When I need the guns...
我就会拿到枪的
I'll get the guns.
Henry?
起来  真该死
Get up, damn it!
Henry
Henry  你没事吧?
Henry, are you all right?
怎么了?
What happened?
听我说  你必须爬到通风口
Listen to me, you have to get up into the vents
去那边把数字输入电脑
and enter the numbers in the computer.
我有多久...
How long was I...
拜托  你要抓紧
Please! Go right now.
我们快没时间了
We're running out of time.
好的  好的
OK. Yeah.
当心点
Be careful!
Henry?
Henry  听得到么
Henry, can you hear me?
Henry
来了  是谁?
Yeah, who is it?
是我  John
It's John.
我能进来么?
Can I come in?
当然
Yeah, of course.
有问题么?
Any problems?
没有
No.
你的朋友  在我葬礼上的那个  她叫什么?
Your date at my funeral, she got a name?
Helen
真是个好名字  长得也很漂亮
That's a nice name. Pretty girl, too.
我  呃...
I'm...
我准备向她求婚
I'm going to ask her to marry me.
就今晚
Tonight, actually.
恩  祝你好运
Well, good for you.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
恩  谢谢
Yeah, thanks.
你的那份  足够你安排一个美妙的蜜月了
Your share. Should buy you a nice honeymoon.
我不是为钱才这么做的
I didn't do this for the money.
那你为什么这么做?
Then why did you do it?
呃... 好吧
Well... All right.
呃... 我的飞机  出租车在等我
My plane... I got a cab waiting.
如果你不想要这些钱
If you don't want the cash,
这儿的服务员的小费可就多了
the maid's gonna get a hell of a tip.
再见  John
Bye, John.
你就是他爸?
Are you him?
听我说  亲爱的...
Listen, sweetheart, I...
你怎么能这样?
How could you?
你怎么能这么对他?
How could you do this to him?
我们已经忘了这些了
We were moving past this!
Helen  等等
Helen, wait.
Helen  等等  你不明白
Helen, wait. You don't understand.
我正准备告诉你一切
I was gonna tell you.
-你骗了我  -不  等等  我能解释
-You lied.  -I can explain.
你当面向我说谎
and you lied to me.
-你已经做了选择  John  -不
-You've made your choice, John.  -No
比起我来你更需要他的爱
You need his love more than mine.
不  我的选择是你  我正要...
No! My choice is you. I was gonna...
我爱你  我...
I love you. I...
不  等等  求你了  等等  Helen
No, no, please, please. Please, Helen...
拜托  我爱你
Please. I love you
而且  我想和你共度余生
and I want to spend my life with you
我不能没有你  Helen
and I can't live without you, Helen.
所以...
So, will...
So...
你愿意嫁给我么?
Will you marry me?
Helen
Henry
Henry...
说话啊
Please say something.
Henry
有人么?
Anybody here?
Is anybody here?
Henry
你回来了
You came back.
怎么  你以为我就把你一人留在这?
What, did you think I was gonna leave you here?
来吧
Come on.
你可以站起来么?
Can you stand?
我不能...
I don't...
我想可以
I think so.
谢谢  Henry
Thank you, Henry.
谢谢你没离开我
Thank you for not leaving me.
不客气  John
You're welcome, John.
嘿  嘿  Jack  等等
Hey. Hey, Jack. Wait up.
你要回舱子里去?
You heading back to the hatch?
是的
Yeah.
我可以一起去么?
Mind if I join?
我很久没洗澡了
It's been a while since I had a shower
我希望...
and I was just hoping that...
事实上  水管出了点问题
Actually, the plumbing's busted.
-坏了?  -是啊  水里都是泥
-Busted?  -The water's been running muddy.
我想有根管子破了
I guess we got a cracked pipe,
但是要找到原因还得再过一段时间
but it's gonna take some time to find it.
哦  这样啊  我想这么多路我是白走了
Oh. Well, I guess I wasted a trip then.
那么  一旦我处理好
Well, I'll let you know as soon as
我尽快告诉你
we get things worked out down there.
好的
OK.
很高兴你打败了Sawyer
I'm glad you beat Sawyer.
你知道么?  我可以明早再去舱子里
You know what? The hatch can wait until morning
不如陪你回海滩吧
if you'd like me to walk you back to the beach.
你看见了么?
Do you see that?
是的
Yeah.
一个降落伞
It's a parachute.
等等
Wait.
是食物
It's food.
那到底是什么?
What the bloody hell is that?
你们找到了什么?
What did you find?
-我抓稳你了  -慢点  慢点
-I gotcha.  -Easy, easy.
抱歉
Sorry.
你怎么...你怎么做到的
What did you do...what did you do to end it
怎么把门弄上去的?
and make the doors go up?
我就做了你跟我说的
I did what you told me to.
我输入了数字
I punched in the code
按了执行键
and I pressed the "execute" button,
但什么事都没发生
but nothing happened
那个钟却倒了回去
other than that clock flipping back.
我正要爬回通风口
I was just climbing back into the vent
灯全灭了
when the lights went out.
十秒钟后  门就开了
Ten seconds later the doors went up.
我什么都没做
I didn't do anything.
你的意思是这都是巧合?
You think it was all just random?
别问我  这是你们的舱子
Don't look at me. It's your hatch.
离他远点
Get away from him.
等等  你不知道...
Wait, you don't...
-给我退后  -Sayid  没事的
-Step back, right now.  -Sayid, it's OK.
我说了  后退
I said, get away!
没事的  是我放他出来的
It's all right. I let him out.
这儿发生了很多事
There was some kind of lockdown or something.
他...他在帮我
He...He was helping me.
你没找到我的热气球么?
Couldn't you find my balloon?
是的  我们找到了
Yeah. We found it.
我们找到了你的热气球 Henry Gale
We did find your balloon, Henry Gale.
就像你所描述的一样
Exactly how you described it.
我们也找到了你说的坟墓
We also found the grave you described.
你妻子的坟
Your wife's grave.
你说的你徒手挖的坟墓
The grave you said you dug with your own bare hands.
全都在
It was all there.
你的整个故事  你的托辞...
Your whole story. Your alibi...
都是真的
It was true.
但是我还是不相信那是真的
But still I did not believe it to be true.
所以我挖开了坟墓
So, I dug up that grave.
我发现里面不是个女人
and found that there was not a woman inside,
而是一个男人
there was a man.
一个叫Henry Gale的男人
A man named Henry Gale.
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====